Guide to the Cornell University News Service records, [ca. 1920s-2000s].
Cornell University News Service records
- Series VI. Cornell University News Services records, 1920s-2000s
  - Subseries VIb. Photographs
    - Science (Research, Labs, and Experiments)
      - Veterinary College - Experiments, 1976 (Box 4-3-15 - 97, Folder 29)
      - Veterinary College - Diagnostic Lab, 1976-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 97, Folder 30)
      - Veterinary College, 1978-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 97, Folder 31)
      - Veterinary College, 1979-1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 97, Folder 32)
      - Veterinary College - Classrooms, 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 97, Folder 33)
      - Veterinary College, 1983-1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 97, Folder 34)
      - Veterinary College, 1989-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 97, Folder 35-36)
      - Copied slides: Virus, 3/5/89; 0241 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Water Filtration Plant, 1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 97, Folder 37)
      - Wellness Program, 1989-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 97, Folder 38)
      - WHCU Antenna Being Taken Down, Mount Pleasant, 1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 97, Folder 39)
- Series VII. Cornell University News Service records, Audio and Visual Material
  An extensive amount of tape recordings and movie films exists as part of this collection. Paper lists may exist, but not all the items have been listed online at this point.
  - A partial list of the tapes can be found here: http://rmc.library.cornell.edu/EAD/pdf_guides/Tape_Recording_Inventory.pdf